Thank you.
Because of you, Father is free.
We won.
Why are you following me?
I'm going with you.
You've given up on Joey.
She likes someone else.
Did she say that?
If I go after what I want,
I will not stop
until she's mine.
Why are you still there?
If you don't want
to force me to kick you out,
leave now!
Don't worry about it.
Be thankful he's just asking you
to hide.
I want my revenge.
I'll even take a video of her
while I kill her.
Call it poetic justice.
I'm a little hesitant
about Jin Ho
searching for Theresa Park
because he doesn't want
to cooperate with the police.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Get out of the car.
Get out!
I'm so happy you caught me.
I'm in trouble.
I need you, Baby.
I was going to talk to you two.
I'm going home to my place.
I want to be with my family.
Of course, you've been dreaming
about it for a long time.
If you need anything, just call.
See you around, Boss Budol.
See you, JoeyOnDuty.
You left me.
Let's finish what we started
together.
You should take care those kinds
of friends.
I hope we can be together again
without any trouble.
Now that we're not worried
about Theresa,
let's focus on the real problem.
He can't make us look weak,
Matias.
I'll take care of that, Berdugo.
Our school starts next week.
Besides, even though I'm already
in studying in Manila,
I'll still come here
every weekend.
Oh my,
you know,
my plan,
is to say goodbye
to Ma'am Yvette.
now that your father
is back home.
Aren't you going to volunteer
anymore, Mother?
You know, Clarissa, if you're
happy with that foundation,
why are you quitting?
I'll take care of the house
first.
- Really?
- Yes, of course!
You know...
You know, I'm really happy
with my job.
It's a great feeling
when you help people.
See.
And you, Father,
what's your plan?
Are you going to be
a househusband?
Are you not going back
to the service?
You know, Joey, all I know
how to do is police work.
But if I go back to the service,
I'll let you know.
Really?
Is that true?
Yes.
Joey, we'll just believe him
if he's going to pull this
and the tower doesn't fall.
That's the only time we'll
believe him.
Really?
Okay.
This, this, this.
If it doesn't collapse.
- I told you!
- No!
I told you you're not going
to be left behind here.
It slipped!
- You know your father.
- Promise, it just slipped!
Hey!
I don't know if I should
congratulate you
because I know what you've been
through was not easy.
But I'm happy that you've
overcome all that.
Your acquittal is final.
You're also out of trouble
with internal affairs.
You're really free now,
Major Delgado.
Thank you very much, Chief.
About your re instatement...
I took the liberty of sending
a recommendation.
All that's missing
is a formal request from you.
I'll take care of the approval.
Chief, if I could,
I'd give my family
some time first.
Miguel, you are one of the good
ones in the force.
There are only a few of you.
Besides, I know you.
You wouldn't be at peace if you
didn't catch the syndicate
that's going after you.
But Mother's calmer now,
since the last time
I visited her, right?
I noticed that too.
You know, it's been a while
since she softened up like that.
That's it. I hope it continues.
Including her giving attention
to me.
You know, she just needs time.
Anyway, who are you interviewing
in Bolagos?
It's Major Miguel Delgado,
Yvette.
Are you interviewing
Miguel Delgado?
Yeah.
Isn't your show focused on
exposés?
And let's be honest, Andrew.
Your show is a bit anti-police.
Yes, and that's exactly
what I want to change, Tomas.
I'm not actually anti-police.
I'm anti-lies, anti-crime,
and anti-corruption.
Because I believe there
are still good police officers,
and Major Miguel Delgado
is one of them.
It's funny that you sound
very impressed with him,
knowing that you don't know him
that well.
Fair point, Hon,
but we shouldn't be judging too
quickly.
Remember, that's why we wanted
to help Clarissa back then.
I know, I just don't want Andrew
walking in blind.
It's hard to trust
someone you don't really know.
Well, I've talked to him
a couple of times
during the investigation, Tomas,
and I think I know enough
to know that he's a good one.
So what exactly do you know?
Hold on. Excuse me.
Yes, Peter? You called.
I am worried about Jin Ho.
He still hasn't come home
since he said he'd keep
an eye on Theresa.
That was just the other day.
Wait. No text or call, nothing?
Nothing, Bro. Cannot be reached.
Okay, maybe he caught Theresa
and took her to South Korea.
Wow, Seriously?
What? He didn't even say
goodbye, just like that?
Well, Peter,
we barely know this guy.
What if he's really like that?
After a mission, it's over,
he goes home.
No attachments.
Andrew knows a lot about
Delgado.
And the way he talks about him,
it's obvious that he's on
his side.
I tried to keep him out
of this mess,
but this is what he wants.
Your brother-in-law is really
a liability, Berdugo.
He'll give Delgado a scene.
He wants to make him a hero.
Well, okay,
let's give it to him.
Major!
Andrew! How are you?
I'm sorry, it's a bit difficult
to come here to Bolagos,
and then I'm late.
It's okay, Major,
it's just a few minutes.
I'm sorry.
Joey, is she there?
She's not here.
She's at home with his mother.
Do you need anything from her?
Andrew, what do you need?
- Let's go set up, Kyle.
- That's what I said.
It's about Jin Ho.
Peter told me he hasn't been
home since the surveillance.
Jin Ho?
I know he's South Korean
intelligence, right?
Don't worry,
I'll talk to my colleagues
at the precinct.
I'll see if they have any
information about this guy.
Okay.
Let's go, Major.
When the camera is pointed
at Delgado,
he stops being a reporter.
He becomes his weapon
to bring us down.
And I can't afford a weapon
being pointed at us,
even if he is family.
I guess some things
really never stay solid.
What now, Berdugo?
Should I include him with
what I'm cooking for Delgado?
Not really,
but I want you to send him
and Delgado a warning.
Make it loud and make it
personal.
Copy, Berdugo.
I released the exposé
to the public, Major,
and I have to own up to that.
I'm responsible for that,
not because I want to,
but because that's my job,
to lay out information.
But it's also my duty
to fix my mistake,
especially when life
and reputation depend on it.
Major, I just want to ask.
When everything was against you,
what do you hold onto to keep
you from giving up?
Of course, it's the truth.
I know it's not my fault.
I don't care what
other people say.
But the worst part of it was
that my own family doubted me.
When they lost trust in me,
that was probably the worst pain
I've ever felt,
and how can I regain that trust?
I'm doing all this for them.
I'm fighting for them.
I'm also grateful to the others
who I never thought
would help me.
But the fight isn't over yet,
Major.
The ones in the video,
alias Theresa Park and alias
Loloy are still at large.
And of course, the head of
the syndicate that set you up,
and also at large.
You know, you're right.
Like as they say,
"We're just getting
to the exciting part."
As long as those syndicates
are there,
those drugs won't run out.
And that will ruin a lot
of young lives.
So we must destroy them.
Let's finish them off.
Matias.
It's ready, Berdugo.
The syndicate will definitely
come back for you, Major.
This Major's life is dangerous.
For sure, there's a bounty on
his head as if he had no family.
They might get into trouble
with you.
Major, have you thought of a way
to expose those syndicates?
You know, Andrew...
What happened?
What's that?
Why did it disappear?
Our live was cut.
Hey!
He blew our tire.
Crazy! Who is that?
Who else knows about this
interview?
A lot, Major.
We advertised your interview
so that many people can watch.
Call him.
Hello, Joey?
Hello, Father?
Miguel?
How are you?
We're fine.
Are you sure?
And Andrew?
He's okay...
No one was hurt. We're fine.
Miguel, go home!
Go home, quick!
Okay, okay, I'm on my way home.
Be careful, Father.
What happened?
My God.
I think they're targeting me.
Target?
But why did they target the bus?
Why didn't he come
after you inside?
Maybe a warning so I don't talk.
Oh my, maybe we're being
warned too, Andrew.
We've covered for Major Delgado
a few times already.
Maybe we seemed like we're on
his allies.
What's that?
Wait, what are we going to do,
Boss?
I still love my life.
Let's be careful.
But that doesn't mean
we're going to give up
just because we were
intimidated.
They can't win.
Evil will prevail even more
when no one fights back,
so we won't give up.
Hello, Yvette?
Yeah, we're good, I'm good.
No one got hurt, thankfully.
Okay.
Father...
Thank God you're safe.
Father, how are you?
Did you find out
who did that to you?
You've only been out
for a few days,
and something like this
is happening?
There's something I wanted
to tell you.
I know you don't want trouble,
but I can't abandon my duty
as a police officer.
As long as those syndicates
are around,
they'll ruin many lives.
Andrew is right.
Evil prevails when no one
fights back.
So I'm going back
to the service.
I'm going to finish this fight.
If it were me, Miguel,
I wouldn't allow you.
I don't want to repeat the
hardship we went through before.
But I love you,
and I know that if I stop you,
you'll regret it for the rest
of your life
that you didn't do anything.
So whatever your decision is,
I'm on your side.
Thank you.
Clarissa,
after this mission is over,
I'll retire.
That's a promise.
We're just here for you, Father.
Never say die?
Never say die.
This is an important day not
only for the Bolagos Police
but for the entire police force.
Today, we are reinstating one
of our brave police officers.
By the authority vested in me
as Bolagos chief of police
and upon the directive
of the Regional command,
I hereby reinstate you
to service,
Major Miguel Delgado.
Welcome back, Major Delgado.
Reporting for duty, Sir!
I can see Delgado.
Sorry.
Wait a minute.
Do you know Major?
Just passing by, Sir.
I looked, and there were a lot
of people.
Okay, Sir.
The day isn't over yet.
I'll finish you later.
What else do you need?
Just a moment, Mother.
Okay.
Andrew, you might choke.
Thank you.
I'm rushing to preview
the footage
so I can send it to my editor.
Thank goodness,
none of your belongings
were damaged on the bus
when you and Father
were attacked.
Actually,
two tires were damaged,
but I got them fixed
so we can go back to Manila.
It's a good thing we met today.
Did you miss me?
Of course!
I mean, of course,
I miss that we're complete,
with Jin Ho and Peter.
You know,
you're really assuming!
Am I really the one assuming?
You said you missed me.
No, no!
What I mean is when we were
together.
I'll go ahead,
I've been bothering you.
This is the coordination letter
you requested.
Whatever you heard,
it can't get out.
What's up with the town
of Balmora?
The deal is already sealed.
He still wants to see me
in person.
But once we meet,
the deal is sealed.
Hey!
It's me!
Big brother!
Peter!
I missed you! It's been a while!
I'm going to give you something.
So you won't forget Mother
and me.
We've already prepared
everything we need for him.
It's his first day
in the service,
and his last day in the world.
The thorn in our throats
is gone.
Have you seen this?
Do not contact me again.
- Joey's father is dead, Jin Ho.
- What?